digitalsports.com 2008-06-23

# DigitalSports - Privacy Policy

**IT’S ABOUT THE KIDS**

We have in place policies and systems for preventing inappropriate content from appearing on our Websites and to prevent any outside content of the kids 

PRIVACY POLICY 

Welcome to DigitalSports and the DigitalSports Network (collectively referred to as "DigitalSports"). Your privacy is important to us at DigitalSports. To help ensure a rewarding online experience for you, we provide you with this summary of our online information practices and privacy notice which governs the collection and use of information on the DigitalSports Network. All Products and Services on the DigitalSports Network are made available subject to this Privacy Policy. The DigitalSports Network collects a variety of information from its users and participants in order to provide the Products and Services (as defined in our Terms and Conditions). The information you provide to us is used in a variety of ways depending on the Products and Services you select. For example, some of our users provide participant information [such as individual or team statistics, game photographs, or general team or player information] specifically for the purpose of public viewing on the Web site. In contrast, our users may also provide personal information when registering for certain Products and Services which is not intended to be publicly viewed or shared outside the DigitalSports Network. The distinctions between the information provided to or collected by DigtalSports and the use and sharing of such information is more specifically described below. 

By using the DigitalSports Network, you agree, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by this Privacy Policy or any other privacy or data collection policy applicable to any individual DigitalSports Network Web site. You will receive any required legal notices regarding our privacy practices through the continuous posting of a clear and conspicuous link near the bottom of most pages to the current version of this Privacy Policy throughout the DigitalSports Network. If you become an inactive user, we will adhere to the policies and practices, which may be revised from time to time, as described in this Privacy Policy. 

Please note that the DigitalSports Network contains links to other sites and occasionally allows other sites to be co-branded with the DigitalSports name. Web sites that are linked to the DigitalSports Network sites or carry the DigitalSports brand for co-branding or marketing purposes may have privacy policies which differ from that of the DigitalSports Network. 

The DigitalSports Network Privacy Policy discloses our privacy practices and contains detailed information about the following: 

WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT 

The goal of the DigitalSports Network is to become your favorite Internet destination by providing the information, services, and rich-media offerings that are most relevant to you. To achieve this goal, the DigitalSports Network collects information from our users so we can understand what makes them different from other unique users. While you are not required to register for any services on the DigitalSports Network, some Products and Services may not function properly or may not be accessible unless you do. 

I. INFORMATION PROVIDED BY VISITORS AND REGISTRANTS 

Visitor Private Personal Information 

To enable visitors to participate in some of the DigitalSports Network activities, and to take advantage of our offerings, DigitalSports collects certain types of information which may include your name, postal address, ZIP Code, e-mail address, birth date, gender, and telephone number (collectively referred to as "Private Personal Information"). Credit card information may be collected if you make an on-line purchase; however, DigitalSports does not retain any credit card information after the purchase. This is done to protect your privacy and preclude the possibility that your credit card information might be misused. While not all of this Private Personal Information is required for the DigitalSports Network Products and Services to function, DigitalSports is better able to customize your experience if you volunteer complete and accurate information. DigitalSports uses Private Personal Information for our internal purposes, which allows DigitalSports to notify visitors of upcoming events and tournaments, to respond to e-mail messages sent to us, and to process requests for our Products and Services. From time to time, DigitalSports may use Private Personal Information to offer visitors opportunities to learn about additional programs, Products or Services that may be of interest to them. WE ARE COMMITTED TO SAFEGUARDING PRIVATE PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED ONLINE. WE DO NOT SHARE YOUR PRIVATE PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH COMPANIES OUTSIDE THE DIGITALSPORTS NETWORK WITHOUT YOUR CONSENT. 

Registration for Products and Services 

Certain Products and Services, including the ability to send messages, upload, post, transmit or input information including codes, data, text, software, music, sounds, photographs, images, pictures, graphics, video, files, or other materials ("Content"), are available only to visitors who register for the DigitalSports Network's Products and Services. Registrants may be asked to provide their name, postal address, ZIP Code, e-mail address, birth date, gender, telephone number, and credit card information, the school or organization contact's name, e-mail, telephone number, and other organizational information (e.g., type of organization, number of teams in your organization, and sports your organization supports) (collectively referred to as "Registration Information") and to verify the age and authority of the individual seeking to use the DigitalSports Network Product and Services. DigitalSports also uses Registration Information to facilitate participation in the DigitalSports Network, and to communicate with our registrants about programs, events, products or services about which they might be interested. WE ARE COMMITTED TO SAFEGUARDING REGISTRATION INFORMATION COLLECTED ONLINE. WE DO NOT SHARE YOUR REGISTRATION INFORMATION WITH COMPANIES OUTSIDE THE DIGITALSPORTS NETWORK WITHOUT YOUR CONSENT. 

Registrants are issued passwords upon registration, allowing information to be input in a secured area. Registrants are able to upload, post, transmit or input information for posting on the DigitalSports Network, about their team, organization or tournament; including information about individual athletes ("Student Profiles"), team statistics, and game information. Registrants also can submit "headlines" with a brief game synopsis. 

When you use the DigitalSports Network to post, upload or transmit Content, the Content is stored in our computers for varying periods of time and is associated with the Registration Information for your account. DigitalSports will not use or disclose such Content except as described in this Privacy Policy. Moreover, when you register for a Product or Service within the DigitalSports Network, that information is collected and maintained solely by the DigitalSports Network unless specifically stated otherwise at the point of collection. If data is collected and/or maintained by any company other than DigitalSports, we will tell you at the point of collection. If you do not want to share your Registration Information with that company, you can choose not to use that service. 

Be aware that DigitalSports Network sponsors and other advertisers have links on the Network that take you to external sites. Some of these sites may collect private personal information from you. Third-party advertising networks may use cookies in their advertisements to collect certain information from you. While DigitalSports hopes that all third-parties involved adhere to our policies regarding the privacy of our users, the DigitalSports Network Privacy Policy does not cover third-party data collection practices. The DigitalSports Network does not assume any responsibility for any actions of third-parties. 

DigitalSports Internet Safety Tips for KIDS 

Keep your passwords private from EVERYONE, even from your neighbors and best friend! Your online service will never ask for them, so neither should anyone else. Use only your log-in name and/or e-mail address when chatting or sending e-mail. Never give out personal information like your name, address, or phone number. Don't share photos of yourself, your family, or your home with people you meet online. Always delete unknown e-mail attachments without opening them. They can contain destructive viruses. If a person writes something that is mean or makes you feel uncomfortable, don't respond. Just log off and tell your parents, who can report it to your online service provider. Remember that nothing you write on the Web is completely private -- including e-mail. So be careful and think about what you type and who you tell. Not everyone is as nice, cute, and funny as they may sound online. Never make plans to meet an online "friend" in person. WHEN IN DOUBT -- always ask your parents for help -- and just LOG OFF if you're not sure! You can always go back online later. 

GetNetWise 

GetNetWise is an online resource for families that, with the click of a mouse, will deliver information and tools needed to guide children to a safe, enriching experience online. Functioning as an interactive directory, GetNetWise contains aggregated and syndicated content that can be found by clicking on the www.getnetwise.org. It is the result of a broad industry effort to create an online environment where families feel empowered with the tools and information they need to safeguard children while providing access to an unprecedented wealth of global resources, information, and contacts available on the Internet. 

Information Collected in Connection with College Recruiting Services 

As part of our future college recruiting service ("CRS"), we plan to have a student’s or student-athletes’ personal information accessible to college recruiters in certain areas of the DigitalSports Network through the use of Digital Athletic Profiles ("DAP"). The CRS will be available on a subscription basis only and access to the secured database housing athletes' personal information will require a password. The student and student-athlete athlete profile will be viewable in a secured area by subscribers for the purpose of college recruiting only. If you are a student or student- athlete using our CRS, you agree to disclosure of personal information which may include: address, phone number, e-mail address, physical statistics, athletic ability, skills, references, SATs, GPAs, and transcripts. If an athlete is under 18 years of age, a parent or guardian is required to give written consent authorizing disclosure of the data. This athlete profile will be viewable in a secured area by subscribers for the purpose of college recruiting only. 

If you need to view, modify or remove your athlete profile, contact us by writing to: 

DigitalSports, Inc.   
8945 Guilford Road Suite 130   
Columbia, MD 21046   
(800) 778-1450   
(410) 344-7822 fax   

II. INFORMATION COLLECTED ELECTRONCALLY FROM ALL USERS 

Anonymous Information 

DigitalSports collects anonymous information, which refers to data that cannot be tied back to a specific individual. For example, DigitalSports collects some information each time a visitor comes to the DigitalSports Network site which assists in improving the overall quality of the visitor's online experience. DigitalSports also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you Products or Services. DigitalSports collects the visitor's IP address (e.g., whether the user is logged on from ibm.com or aol.com), referral data (e.g., the Internet address of the last Web page visited by a user before clicking over to the DigitalSports Network site), and browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform). In addition, DigitalSports collects your responses to online surveys displayed on the DigitalSports Network. The anonymous and optional surveys seek your opinions about the Products and Services or the advertisements displayed on the DigitalSports Network. You do not have to register with the DigitalSports Network before we can collect this anonymous information. 

DigitalSports may collect anonymous information and share it with third-party advertisers in an aggregate form. DigitalSports will disclose to those advertisers the numbers of DigitalSports users who have certain demographic characteristics and the number of those people who have seen and "clicked" on a particular display. DigitalSports may also disclose to those advertisers the overall demographics available regarding who saw and "clicked" on their advertisement. In addition, DigitalSports may disclose anonymous results from online surveys to third-party advertisers. No Private Personal Information or Registration Information will be disclosed as part of this process. 

DigitalSports may also use the aggregate data to perform statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our Registrants and visitors, to measure user demographics and interests regarding specific areas of the DigitalSports Network, and to analyze how and where best to use our resources. DigitalSports does not track what pages individual users are browsing, but rather how well each page performs overall. Without such data, DigitalSports would not know which parts of the DigitalSports Network are the most popular and would not be able to change and update the Content and Services appropriately. 

If you told DigitalSports that you were interested in receiving offers or information from selected sponsors and advertisers, DigitalSports or third-parties on DigitalSports' behalf will send you e-mail about Products and Services that we feel may be of interest to you. By electing to receive such materials directly from selected sponsors or advertisers you automatically consent to the release of your Private Personal Information or Registration Information to the applicable sponsor or advertiser. DigitalSports may also combine information we have about you with information we obtain about you from third parties for the purpose of providing you with more appropriate Products, Services, and offerings. If you do not wish to have us combine information supplied in the DigitalSports Network registration process with information obtained from third-parties, please contact us at: 

DigitalSports, Inc.   
8945 Guilford Road Suite 130   
Columbia, MD 21046   
(800) 778-1450   
(410) 344-7822 fax   
Email: techsupport@digitalsports.com 

Use of Cookies 

DigitalSports may collect anonymous information passively using cookies. This technology plays an important role in making the Internet work, but there is much confusion among Internet users about what cookies are and how they are used. 

DigitalSports currently uses something called a "session cookie". This is a serialized number that is shared by the DigitalSports server with your Internet browser program each time you visit the web site. The session cookie only persists for the duration of your visit on the DigitalSports web site. The Session Cookie is dismissed when you close your Internet browser program (or time-out after 20 minutes of inactivity). This is the least intrusive type of cookie. A session cookie is just a number. It does not retain your personal information. 

The second type of cookie is called a "persistent cookie". This is a small text file containing a unique identification number that is transferred from a web site to the hard drive of your computer so that the site administrator may identify your computer and passively track its activities on the web site. This unique number identifies your Web browser whenever you visit the original web site. A persistent cookie will not allow a Web site to learn any Private Personal Information or Registration Information that you have not otherwise disclosed. Unlike the majority of other web sites, the DigitalSports system does NOT employ persistent cookies. 

It is possible to adjust your Web browser preferences to alert you when a cookie is sent to your Internet browser, or to refuse cookies altogether. DigitalSports requires the use of "session cookies" for coaches, athletic directors, MyCombine Subscribers, and others who login and update information. DigitalSports does NOT require other web site visitors to use cookies, either "session cookies" or "persistent cookies". 

III. SHARING OF INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THE DIGITALSPORTS NETWORK 

Disclosure to Companies within the DigitalSports Network 

By providing DigitalSports with your Private Personal Information or Registration Information, you authorize DigitalSports to internally share that information with other companies or affiliates in the DigitalSports Network, including companies that become part of the DigitalSports Network in the future. 

Any company in the DigitalSports Network (including DigitalSports) is authorized to share your Private Personal Information with any other affiliate or web site in the DigitalSports Network for the following purposes: to manage, administer, provide, expand and improve the existing DigitalSports Network Products and Services, and to offer new Products and Services; to adapt such Products and Services to your tastes and preferences; to send service updates to DigitalSports visitors, users and Registrants; to send, by traditional and/or electronic means, technical, operational and commercial information relating to the Products and Services offered by the DigitalSports Network or through any of the sites operated by the DigitalSports Network, currently and in the future; and to send survey forms, which you are not required to fill in. DigitalSports and the DigitalSports Network will always give you the option to opt out of receiving any information or notices as described above, other than legal notices and other notices that are necessary to the functioning of the Products and Services, during the time that you are using the Products and Services or maintain an active registration with the DigitalSports Network. In any event, DigitalSports will take precautions to maintain the confidentiality and security of all user information sent abroad. 

Disclosure to Third-Parties 

The DigitalSports Network maintains relationships with third-parties in connection with co-branded Web sites. Co-branded sites are operated by third-party companies and offer a particular Service or Product to DigitalSports Network users. We also maintain private label relationships where a third-party company provides us with technology, services and/or Content under DigitalSports Network branding. When you provide Private Personal Information or Registration Information, you automatically consent to the sharing of this information with the third-party companies or organizations providing these services. You should make every effort to read the individual privacy policies of such third-parties and make an informed decision on your own whether or not to provide Private Personal Information or Registration Information based upon these providers privacy practices and your own discretion. 

DigitalSports may disclose Private Personal Information and Registration Information to third-party service providers who agree to maintain the confidentiality of such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Any use of your Private Personal Information or Registration Information will be strictly limited to the support services provided to DigitalSports, including, without limitation, processing and storing user information, helping to create new Content and promotions for the DigitalSports Network, and sending or coordinating the sending of marketing communications to users that have elected to receive them. 

DigitalSports will disclose Private Personal Information and Registration Information to governmental or judicial authorities or law enforcement agencies, or to other individuals or entities in response to subpoena, court order, or other legal process, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. In matters involving a danger to personal or public safety, DigitalSports may voluntarily provide such information to appropriate governmental authorities. 

OPT-OUT POLICY 

You can opt-out of sharing your Private Personal Information or Registration Information with any third-party service or content providers in any areas of the DigitalSports Network by choosing not to use such areas or by sending us an e-mail at techsupport@digitalsports.com 

If you have a question about the DigitalSports opt-out process that is not answered here, please send an e-mail to techsupport@digitalsports.com 

SECURITY 

We have appropriate security measures in place to prevent unauthorized access to information that we collect online. The DigitalSports Network has security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of user data under our control. DigitalSports uses physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect any Private Personal Information and data stored on its computers. Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, only authorized employees have access to the information you provide the DigitalSports Network. Any particularly sensitive information, such as a credit card number used to purchase particular Products or Services, is encrypted prior to transmission. 

While DigitalSports cannot guarantee loss, misuse or alteration to data, DigitalSports takes many precautions to prevent such unfortunate occurrences. 

You are ultimately responsible for the security of your DigitalSports user name and password and care should be taken when using and storing your DigitalSports user name and password. DigitalSports recommends that you do not divulge your password to anyone. You should log out of your Web browser at the end of each computer session to ensure that others cannot access your Private Personal Information and correspondence, especially if several people have access to your personal computer or you are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe. 

Credit card numbers: DigitalSports will, as required for ecommerce purposes, display secured web pages and ask for credit card numbers. Your credit card number is used to authorize the transaction and then discarded. It has been our policy from the beginning that we do not save or retain credit card numbers. 

A SPECIAL NOTE FOR PARENTS 

IT’S ABOUT THE KIDS 

We have in place policies and systems for preventing inappropriate content from appearing on our Websites and to prevent any outside content of the kids 

Unlike many other Internet sites, this site is not directed at children (individuals under the age of 13), nor does it knowingly collect personal information online from them without the permission of their parents or guardians. The Internet offers a world of opportunity for children. Your guidance and involvement are essential to help ensure that children have a safe and rewarding online experience. 

Congress also has passed a federal law, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) of 1998, which helps protect children in their online activities by regulating the online collection of personal information from individuals under the age of 13. 

To obtain more information on COPPA, visit http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/buspubs/coppa.htm or additional information can be obtained at the following links: 

Department of Education: Parents Guide to the Internet   
http://www.ed.gov/pubs/parents /internet/ 

Better Business Bureau (BBB)   
http://www.bbbonline.com 

Electronic Frontier Foundation - non-profit dedicated to protecting public interest in online privacy. http://www.eff.org 

Net Nanny - child safety software that filters potentially harmful Web sites. http://www.netnanny.com/ 

CHANGES TO OUR POLICY 

This policy, like the Internet medium, is subject to change. If we materially change our information practices, we will inform visitors prior to implementing such changes. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. 

CONTACT US 

DigitalSports, Inc.   
8945 Guilford Road Suite 130   
Columbia, MD 21046   
(800) 778-1450   
(410) 344-7822 fax   
Email: [techsupport@digitalsports.com](mailto:techsupport@digitalsports.com)
